suzyssitcom.com 2012-12-15

# Disclosures and Privacy Policy | Suzy's Artsy Craftsy Sitcom

---|---  
  
### **_Disclosures:_**

This blog is dedicated to bringing you fun ideas. While I would never knowingly promote a project that is dangerous, some materials and techniques are not appropriate for all ages. Some materials can be toxic (glue, electric lights, etc.) Please use your own good judgment when taking part in these crafts. I make no claims about the safety of any of the projects featured on my blog, or the techniques or supplies used. I take no responsibility for what you choose to do with the information and ideas represented by Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom.

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. I believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

I am sometimes compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely mine. If I claim or appear to be an expert on a certain topic or product or service area, I will only endorse products or services that I believe, based on my expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

### Privacy

**Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom.

**Credit card details**

Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom.

**External Sites.**

Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Suzys Artsy Craftsy Sitcom have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:myers6281@hotmail.com)
